<resources>
        <string name = "app_name"> Colombia Tourism </string>

        <string name = "hello_world"> Hello World! </string>
        <string name = "hoteles"> Hotels in Apartadó </string>
        <string name = "bares"> Bars Apartadó </string>
        <string name = "tourismo">Tourist information in Apartado </string>
        <string name = "demo">Demographics Apartadó</string>

        <string name = "about"> App Creator </string>
        <string name="namecreator">Ricardo Restrepo Angel</string>
        <string name="semestre">Sixth semester</string>
        <string name="study">Electronic Engineering student</string>

        <string name="ubica"> Location in Antioquia</string>
        <string name="bandera">Flag</string>



        <string name = "action_settings"> Settings </string>


        <string name = "title_activity_hotel_activty"> Guide Hotels </string>
        <string name = "title_activity_bares"> Guide Bars </string>
        <string name = "title_activity_turismo"> Tourism </string>
        <string name = "title_activity_demo"> Demographics </string>
        <string name = "title_activity_about"> About </string>

        <string name = "action_hotel"> Hotels </string>
        <string name = "action_bares"> Bars </string>
        <string name = "action_info"> Tourist information  </string>
        <string name = "action_demo"> Demographics </string>
        <string name = "action_about"> About </string>

        <string name="reseña">SUMMARY\n\n
            Apartado is a municipality of Colombia,located in the subregion of Urabá in the department
            Antioquia. It is the largest municipality in the subregion
            Uraba, because it houses the headquarters of
            banana and commercial enterprises. It bordered on the north and west
            with the city of Turbo, on the east by the department of Córdoba
            and on the south by the municipality of Carepa. Its municipal head is
            336 kilometers from the provincial capital, Medellin. In its urban area,
            Section is divided into 49 districts, spread over 4 communes. While
            in its rural, it has 4 corregimientos5 and 57 villages.
        </string>

        <string name="presentacion">
            Apartado prepares to face the challenges that globalization
            and the influx of new people whose culture generate multicultural spaces
            converging in an urban space in which new cultural models are built.\n\n
            Apartadó has one plurietnicocultural wealth that will help us to show our strengths.
            We show tourist sites such as San José de Apartadó, Puerto Girón, banana balers,
            Our Parks and especially our climate becomes our greatest strength, accompanied it in
            education and health to provide our citizens to achieve the Millennium Development Goals
            and objectives of the Development Plan.\n\n
            Apartado Come and find friendly, hardworking people, exceptional landscapes,
            a mixture of cultures that makes the most cheerful and most prolific region of Antioquia,
            empowered some leaders in the development of our region, artistic talent as anyone else
            and an ability to emerge from the social experience we have had.
        </string>

        <string name="extension">Extension: 600 Km^2</string>
        <string name="poblacion">Population: 178,257</string>
        <string name="gentilicio">Gentilicio: Apartadosense, Apartadoseño,-a</string>


        <string name="nombreh1">Hotel Embera</string>
        <string name="nombreh2">Hotel Guateque</string>
        <string name="nombreh3">Hotel el Oscar</string>
        <string name="nombreb1">La 100</string>
        <string name="nombreb2">Party Xtrem</string>
        <string name="nombreb3">Pebbles Pizzeria</string>

        <string name="direccionh1">Calle 100 #103–49</string>
        <string name="direccionh2">Carrera 102 #91–20</string>
        <string name="direccionh3">Carrera 102 #98–10</string>
        <string name="direccionb1">Calle 100 #103–49</string>
        <string name="direccionb2">Carrera 105 Barrio Ortiz</string>
        <string name="direccionb3">Carrera 105 #100f-01</string>

        <string name="telefonoh1">(574)828 15 88</string>
        <string name="telefonoh2">(574)828 84 34</string>
        <string name="telefonoh3">(574)828 81 84</string>
        <string name="telefonob1">(574)828 15 88</string>
        <string name="telefonob2">--</string>
        <string name="telefonob3">(574) 828 31 46</string>

        <string name="guia">Parque de los Encuentros\n\n
            Address: Km. 3 Via Carepa\n
            County: Apartado\n
            Location: Park Meeting-Comfenalco\n
            Description: 46 hectares with swimming pools, recreational diving and recreational programs
        </string>

        <string name="guia2">
            Parque el Oasis\n\n
            Address:. Km 3 route Carepa\n
            Park Services:\n
            Wetland: pool babies, children and adults pool.\n
            Sports area: Football area, beach volleyball court, playground.\n
            Social area: Auditorium and / or meeting room, an indoor lounge for special events (200 people), restaurant, cafeteria and parking.\n
            We also offer: tailored business social events, academic and ..\n
            Social area Meeting rooms, restaurants, nature trails and parking. We also offer: business, academic and social events tailored.
        </string>

        <string name="guia3">
            Parque Zungo\n\n
            Address: 10 minutes by car from the village\n
            Park Services:\n
            Wetland: slide, children and adults swimming pools, sauna, steam, lazy river\n.
            Sports area: Skating rink, soccer, sports plate. Playgrounds, nature trails.\n
            Social area: auditoriums and / or meeting rooms, restaurant, cafeteria and parking.\n
            Accommodation: 8 cabins can accommodate 4 persons per each one\n.
            Ecological Island: Meeting place for training and environmental awareness activities.
        </string>

        <string name="guia4">
            Puerto Giron\n\n
           3. EcoGirón: community ecotourism Puerto Girón is a bastion of biodiversity in the middle
            of banana monoculture, a Chocoano village hidden in Antoquia\n
           4. EcoGirón: community ecotourism ACUA EcoGiron Foundation will support the venture, which
            is developing tourist proposals to promote tourism in the area.
        </string>

        <string name="guia5">
            Banana\n\n
            The main activity of this region is the cultivation of Banana and Plantain exported from here to various
            regions of the world. There are many varieties of bananas, and also make banana cake, chocolate banana,
            panelitas banana, banana coconut candies and more ..
        </string>


</resources>
